Forgive us as we forgive those who what?
Thank you. I hope you are ready.
You are ready? That is your role - put everything behind and look forward.
I stopped looking back. You keep looking back. Those who offended you yesterday - the pain of the past.
Looking back will hinder you from looking forward.
You cannot look back and look forward at the same time - it is not possible.
See!
That is our life. Our life is....
That is, in not forgiving and forgetting the pain of the past, your life is...
But when you forget and forgive the pain of the past...
Can you rise up and demonstrate this to yourself. Speak to yourself.
Say, "For me not to forgive the pain of the past, and forget and forgive,
my life will remain...
Do it!
But if you are now ready to forget and forgive the pain of the past, your life...
The SCOAN Sunday Service